{"data":[{"question":"The Bakers ________ English.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The: used before the name of a family in the plural to refer to all the members of that family.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Let us ________ to school.","a":"go","b":"going","c":"goes","d":"to go","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Let's do something: used when you suggest doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Where are Kate and Jane? - They ________ English exercises in the classroom.","a":"are doing","b":"is doing","c":"are going","d":"are going to do","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the present continuous to say that something happens at the time of speaking\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Tom and Mary are pupils but Ann ________.","a":"isn't","b":"are","c":"is","d":"aren't","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (Ann) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"What ________ the Bakers ________ at the moment?","a":"is \/ doing","b":"are \/ working","c":"are \/ doing","d":"is \/ working","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The + family name: plural.\u00a0\n- Do: used in general question.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"How ________ your parents?","a":"are","b":"is","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject is \"your parents\" (plural).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"What ________ the weather like today?","a":"are","b":"is","c":"were","d":"was","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject is \" the weather\" (singular).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"It ________ very hot yesterday.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"were","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (yesterday).\u00a0\n- Subject is \"it\" (singular).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"My daughter is a teacher. My wife is a teacher, too. They ________ both teachers.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"were","d":"was","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject is \" They\" (plural).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Ben and Jim are ________.","a":"architect","b":"engineer","c":"student","d":"brothers","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Subject (Ben and Jim) is plural\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}